Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Irish Americana Collection AIA.031.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Ephemera, 1883-1928, 191728
  - Merchant Ads, 242158
    - Victor Records (ad), Ladies Home Journal, Feb, 1917; 191770 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Valiant (ad), circa 1960s; 191766 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Irish International Airlines (ad), 1963; 191765 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - The Luck of the Irish (ad), 1948; 191768 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Shillelagh Apples (ad), undated; 191763 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Welcome Answer, The, undated; 242187 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Jameson's Irish American Whiskey (ad), undated; 191764 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Columbia Hour of Musical Broadcasting, Oct 1, 1927; 242188 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Victor - Victrola, Mar 29, 1913; 242189 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Irish Airlines (ad), circa 1960s; 191767 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Globe Clothing House (ad), undated; 191771 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Cartoons, 242167
    - Life in New York, undated; 191754 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - The Fenian Pest, Punch, March 3, 1866; 191736 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Disendowment and Disarmament, Punch, April 13, 1869; 191735 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - An Irish Wake, Harper's Weekly, March 15, 1873; 191744 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - An Axe to Grind, Weekly National Press, Jan, 1892; 242190 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Speak or Die!, Weekly National Press, Mar, 1892; 242191 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - The Irish Skirmishers 'Blind Pool', Puck, undated; 191738 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Last Reception of the Season, Puck, undated; 191739 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - O'Donovan Rossa's Shooting Gallery, Puck, undated; 191737 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral, Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, June 7, 1879; 191751 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Fenian Congress, Harper's Weekly, Nov. 4, 1865; 191750 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Land Agitation, Harper's Weekly, 1880; 191742 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Europe, Church & State, United States, Harper's Weekly, Feb. 1870; 191748 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Would You Marry Your Daughter to a Nigger?, Harper's Weekly, July 1, 1868; 191749 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - The Irish Tempest, Punch, March 19, 1870; 191733 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - The Irish Treason Shop, Punch, Dec. 4, 1869; 191734 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Leading Him a Lively Dance (cartoon), undated; 191753 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Round the Cauldron, Punch, March 26, 1887; 191732 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Waiting for the Return of a Sunday Excursion, The Judge, July 15, 1882; 191741 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - St. Patrick in New York, Harper's Weekly, April 2, 1870; 191747 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Roman Cathlics Disgracing Themselves, Harper's Weekly, May 7, 1870; 191746 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Champion of the Fenians, Harper's Weekly, Oct. 21, 1876; 191743 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - The Usual Irish Way of Doing Things, Harper's Weekly, Sept. 2, 1871; 191745 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Little Orphan Annie, New York Herald, 1904; 191740 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - An Xmas Greeting to Waterford, Weekly National Press, 1891; 191731 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Series VII: Unprocessed, undated; 444735
  Series VII: Unprocessed, undated consists of posters, 19th century illustrations, postcards, sheet music, songsters, advertisements and a piano roll.
  - Posters and 19th century illustrations., undated; 444736 (Box 58)
  - Postcards and a piano roll., undated; 444737 (Box 59)
  - Sheet music, songsters, advertisements and illustrations., undated; 444738 (Box 60, Box 61)